happymassage.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy

﻿

We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This privacy policy is about the way we use the personal information of users. If you use any of our services, this privacy policy applies to you. This policy is effective on 22 May 2013. The policy explains: 

**Protecting your privacy**   
• We don't run banner ads, pop ups, pop unders, or any other kind of commercial ads.   
• We don't share your information with third parties for marketing purposes.   
• We don't engage in cross-marketing or link-referral programs with other sites.   
• We don't employ tracking devices for marketing purposes ("cookies", "web beacons," single-pixel gifs).   
• We don't send you unsolicited communications for marketing purposes.   
• Account information is password-protected. Keep your password safe.   
• If happymassage.com learns that a posting is by a person under the age of 18, we will remove that post.   
• happymassage.com, or people who post on happymassage.com, may provide links to third party websites, which may have different privacy practices. We are not responsible for, nor have any control over, the privacy policies of those third party websites, and encourage all users to read the privacy policies of each and every website visited. 

**Data we collect**   
• We sometimes collect your email address, for purposes such as sending confirmation emails, authenticating user accounts, registering, etc. We may also collect personal information if you provide it in feedback or comments, post it on our classifieds.   
• For postings, we collect contact information, such as name(s), phone(s), and address.   
• happymassage.com does not store credit card information. Credit card transactions are transmitted to a financial gateway, and we endeavor to protect the security of your payment information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. 

**Use**   
We use users' personal information to:   
• provide our services;   
• resolve troubleshoot problems;   
• encourage safe trading and enforce our policies;   
• customize users' experience, and inform users about services and updates;   
• do other things for users as described when we collect the information. 

**About Cookies**   
Many websites, including those owned by happymassage.com, use cookie technology to help users navigate efficiently. The cookie is a small text file that resides on your hard drive. From time to time, our site(s) will request the cookie from your browser so that we can retrieve the stored information. This prevents you from making the same selections over and over again. happymassage.com does not use cookies to store personal information, such as credit-card numbers. Please note that with most browsers, a user can set the preferences to show a warning each time a cookie request is received. You can also usually set the browser not to accept cookies at all. However, to make your experience using our site as convenient as possible, we suggest that you allow your browser to accept cookies. 

**Information Sharing**   
Happymassage.com will not sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information to third parties. Unless we have your permission or are required by law, we will only share the personal data you provide online with other third-party vendors that are acting on our behalf to complete the activities described above. We will cooperate with law enforcement authorities. 

**Security**   
Happymassage.com is committed to protecting the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We use encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. 

**Oversight**   
If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please contact us. 

**Right to Change**   
Happymassage.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence and location of the new or revised Privacy Policy.
